[
    {
        "question" : "1. Not a marvel superhero",
        "answers": ["Thor", "Daredevil", "Black Widow", "The flash"],
        "correct": "The flash"
    },
    {
        "question" : "2. Do the math, 1000 + 10 + 1000 + 20 + 1000 + 30 + 1000 + 40",
        "answers": ["4010", "4100", "4200", "5000"],
        "correct": "4100"
    },
    {
        "question" : "3. What is the color of the stars in the flag of the United States of America?",
        "answers": ["Red", "Blue", "White", "Black"],
        "correct": "White"
    },
    {
        "question" : "4. What's the total number of dots on a pair of dice?",
        "answers": ["41", "42", "43", "44"],
        "correct": "42"
    },
    {
        "question" : "5.Traditionally, how many Wonders of the World are there?",
        "answers": ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
        "correct": "7"
    },
    {
        "question" : "6. What is the chemical symbol for Hydrogen?",
        "answers": ["H", "He", "Hy", "Hg"],
        "correct": "H"
    },
    {
        "question" : "7. How many sides does an octagon have?",
        "answers": ["Six", "Seven", "Eight", "nine"],
        "correct": "Eight"
    },
    {
        "question" : "8.Which part of the body would a chiropodist treat?",
        "answers": ["Hands", "Head", "Feet", "Back"],
        "correct": "Feet"
    },
    {
        "question" : "9. What is the name of the city where the cartoon family The Simpsons live?",
        "answers": ["Hollywood", "Scottsdale", "Summerfield", "Springfield"],
        "correct": "Springfield"
    },
    {
        "question" : "10. Which U.S. president appears on the front of the $2 bill?",
        "answers": ["Thomas Jefferson", "Abraham Lincoln", "George Washington", "Benjamin Franklin"],
        "correct": "Thomas Jefferson"
    }
]
